Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Stuart Elliott papers
1875-2014 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Elliott, Stuart
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11108
85.0 Linear Feet
Advertising and business columnist for USA Today and the New York Times.
Arrangement
Arranged into the following series: General Files; Conferences and Programs; Correspondence; Print Materials; Subject Files; Trade Contacts; Writings Files; Large-Format Materials; and Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical / Historical
Graduate Medill School of Journalism, Northwestern University; worked at Advertising Age, Detroit Free Press and USA Today before joining the New York Times in 1991. Retired 2014.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Stuart Elliott papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2014.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections: Carl Spielvogel papers, Margaret Fishback papers, Alvin A. Achenbaum papers, and the J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising Columnists Articles.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1875-2014 and includes clippings, correspondence, drafts of newspaper articles and weblog posts, subject files and other printed materials relating to Elliott's career as a columnist. Recurring topics include Super Bowl advertising, advertising spending, diversity in advertising industry hiring, gay/lesbian/transgender (LGBT) issues and consumer demographics, agency mergers and client relations, media industry conferences, and media technology innovations. Collection primarily focuses on Elliott's tenure as columnist at the New York Times, but materials representing work at USA Today and the Detroit Free Press are also present. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Gay rights movement -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Gay rights movement -- United States; Gays' writings -- United States; Gay activists -- United States; Gay community -- United States; Gay consumers -- United States; Lesbian consumers -- United States; Lesbian community -- United States; Journalists -- United States -- Correspondence; Journalism -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Advertising -- Periodicals; Advertising; Elliott, Stuart; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- General Files, 1967-2010 and undated; 1
  - 9/11 World Trade Center attacks, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 10th anniversary of Elliott's Times column, 2001; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Articles about/press mentions of Elliott, 1992-2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Caricatures, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CBS Sunday Morning, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Food spokescharacter bracket, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Honolulu Advertiser/Honolulu Star-Bulletin closings, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "In Advertising" email newsletter, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kudos/evaluations, 1992-2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Loose audiovisual items (documents and separation sheets; physical audiovisual moved to Audiovisual Series) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memorials and obituaries, 1979-2010; 2 folders (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Allen Myerson, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Arnold Gingrich, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Arthur Hays Sulzberger, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Dick Dougherty, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Memorials and obituaries--George Lazarus, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Henry Luce, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Memorials and obituaries--James Winston Brady, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Jay Chiat, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Lee Aarons, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Luther Davis, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Paul Tilley, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Philip Dougherty, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Philip Dusenberry, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Philippe Halsman, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Rusty (J. Russell) King, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Ruth Reinke Whitney, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Steven Florio, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Memorials and obituaries--Tom King, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Memorials and obituaries--William Paley, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Network Event Theater, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - New York Times--Announcements, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New York Times--Anthrax scare, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New York Times--Jayson Blair, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - New York Times--Julie Bosman, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - New York Times--Notes and miscellaneous, 1991-2007; 4 folders (Box 2, Folder 19-22)
  - New York Times--Nat Ives, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - New York Times--Position announcement (Elliott), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - New York University, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New Yorker, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter email survey, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated, 3 folders (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
  - Road trip, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Shona Seifort "code of ethics", 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Stuart's Sense and Sensibility"--Tim McHale, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Age of Cross-Media Entertainment Business Plan, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - USA Today, 1988-2004; 2 folders (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Vanity Fair, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vic Sussman, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Conferences and Programs, 1981-2014 and undated; 2
  - AAA conference remarks, circa 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AAAA PR conference, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - AAF National Conference, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - ABC 20/20 episode, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ad Club--Out of Home, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ad Club of Western Michigan, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - AdTech New York, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AdTech New York, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ads Against AIDS, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Advertising Club, 2004, 2013; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 3-3a)
  - Advertising in America Conference, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Advertising Research Foundation, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Advertising ROI Roundtable, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Advertising Week (AdWeek DC), 2007-2011; 11 folders (Box 4, Folder 7-17)
  - Advertising Week (AdWeek DC), 2012-2014; 4 folders (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - Advertising Women of New York, 2000-2011; 3 folders (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers), 2003-2008; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
  - Anne Morgan's War: Rebuilding Devastated France 1917-1924, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Auto Show, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - BBB (Better Business Bureau), 2009-2010; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Big Ad Gig, 2010-2012; 2 folders (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Brain Game, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bravo--Queer Eye for the Straight Guy panel, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Advertising High School, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bruce McCall Retrospective, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cannes, 2005; 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - Center for Communications Conference, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Advertising Federation--Advertising and Popular Culture, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - CMO Council, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CNN Business Writers Forum, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Commercial Closet Association Corporate Visionary Honors, 2006; 2 folders (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - Commercial Closet talk, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Creative Media Summit, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Digital Day, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Digital Technology Panel, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Diversity Stir It Up!, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - DMA All for One Summit, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - DMA Insert Media Day, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - DMIX (Direct Marketing Idea Exchange), 2013 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dream Girls: Images of Women in Advertising 1890s-1990s, American Advertising Museum, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Equality Forum, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Events cancelled due to 9/11, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Executive Marketing Summit, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition--Dixie Sheridan theater photographs, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ExxonMobil lecture on advertising ethics, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fashion Scholarships Fund, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Financial Communications Society Portfolio Awards, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Fragrance Foundation Selling Scents Seminar, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Gay Media Panel, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - George Stephanopolis remarks to National Lesbian Gay Journalists Association, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - I Want My Gay TV Pridevision, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Kenyon College Extern Program, 1996-2007; 5 folders (Box 7, Folder 15-19)
  - Kimpton Hotels Summer of Pride, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Legends of Madison Avenue, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - LGBT Youth Live Out Loud, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Long Island Ad Club, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lotos Club, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - LSU student advertising NYC trip, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mad Men panel, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Week Brands Summit, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Medill Club of NY, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-2014; 7 folders (Box 8, Folder 8-14)
  - Museum of Television and Radio--Madison Avenue Meets Gasoline Alley, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - National Lesbian Gay Journalists Association, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - New Media Panel, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - New York Advertising and Communications Network, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - New York Times--360 Summit, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - New York Times--Breakfast, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - New York Times--Diversity Panel "Multicultural America", 2007; 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - New York Times--Future of Recruitment Advertising, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New York Times--Innovation Council, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New York Times--Lunch, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New York Times--Media Group Sales Conference, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - New York Times--Multicultural Panel, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - New York Times--Multicultural Marketing Panel, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - New York Times--Panel, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - New York Times--Panel--Gay/Lesbian Online Marketplace, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - New York Times--Panel--The Future of Media, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - New York Times--Roundtable--Online Video, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - New York Times--Roundtable--Social Networking, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - New York Times--Talks--Advertising to Gay America, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - New York Times--Talks--I Want My Gay TV!, 2002; 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
  - NLGJA (National Lesbian Gay Journalists Association), 2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NY AMA (American Marketing Association)--Gaming, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NYTech Panel, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Ohio University, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Out Professionals--Building Brands at the Speed of Culture, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Out Professionals--Jack Schlegel Salute, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Out Professionals--Josh Kilmer-Purcell book event, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Out Professionals--Outing Madison Avenue, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Out Professionals--Panel, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Out Professionals--Provocation in Advertising, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Out Professionals--Talk, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Paley Media Center Council panel, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - PEN Festival, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pixels and Print panel (e-learning), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - PR Week, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PR Week Cause Roundtable, 2007; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Princeton Club, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Promax, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations Society of America, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Publicity Club of New York, 2003, 2011; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
  - Queer as Folk, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ReFrame: The Brand, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Reuters--Breaking the Lavender Ceiling panel, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Richard Lewis branding class visit, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - RLTV Rethink 5+ (Boomer Town), 2013 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - San Francisco business talk--Gay/lesbian attitudes, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Scent Marketing Institute ScentWorld Conference, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Silicon Alley Breakfast Club, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Special Libraries Association, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stern School of Business Lesbian and Gay Business Association, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Syracuse University New House School of Public Communications 40th Anniversary, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Targeting Gay and Lesbian Consumers, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Television Bureau of Advertising, 2005-2011; 3 folders (Box 11, Folder 21-23)
  - The Art of Coming Out, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Big Ad Gig Panel, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Dartmouth school newspaper, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ThinkLA Conference, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tom King, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Transformation Conference--Sustainability, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Transformation LA, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Twenty Questions with Richard Kirshenbaum '83, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - University of Wisconsin Writer in Residence, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Upfront notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Open Tennis, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Walking the High Line, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Women's Economic Club, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Yale, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1980s-2012 and undated; 3
  - General, 1980s-2002; 8 folders (Box 13, Folder 1-8)
  - General, 2003-2012; 6 folders (Box 14, Folder 1-6)
  - E-mail, 2000-2003; 7 folders (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - E-mail, 2004-2007 April; 8 folders (Box 16, Folder 1-8)
  - E-mail, 2007 May-2008 September; 6 folders (Box 17, Folder 1-6)
  - E-mail, 2008 October-2010 May; 7 folders (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
  - E-mail, 2010 June-2012; 4 folders (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - E-mail re Mad Men episode, 2010 (Folder 5)
  - Holiday greeting cards, 1990s-2000s; 3 folders (Folder 6-8)
  - Holiday greeting cards, 1990s-2000s; 6 folders (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
  - Holiday greeting cards, 1990s-2000s; 5 folders (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
  - Holiday greeting cards, 1990s-2000s; 3 folders (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Kudos, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Notables, 1990s-2000s; 4 folders (Box 22, Folder 5-8)
- Print Materials, 1940-2013 and undated; 4
  - 100 Years of Food History, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - A Brain Is for Eating (Dan and Ameila Jacobs, Humanaut), 2013 (Folder 2)
  - Advertising Age Datacenter, 2007-2008 (Folder 3)
  - Advertising Go-cards and postcards, undated, 5 folders (Folder 4-8)
  - Ad Week, 2006-2008 (Folder 9)
  - Andy Warhol's Diaries Index, 1985 (Folder 10)
  - (Baron Adolph) De Meyer A Singular Elegance, 1994 (Folder 11)
  - Be Careful What You Wish For...It Might Come True (Lynn Woodward), 1994 (Folder 12)
  - Benetton--We, On Death Row, 2000 (Folder 13)
  - Best Thing on TV: Commercials (Jonathan Price), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Better World Advertising--Gay and Bisexual Men's Television Viewing Patterns, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Beyond the Wall, 1996 January (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - BMO Capital Markets: Broadcasting, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Brand Week, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Brand Week: Superbrands, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Cartoons, 1987-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - CBS--Brand: Exploring the Network's Identity, circa 1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - CBS Broadcast Guide: Winter Olympics Nagano, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Cheerios: First 60 Years, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Coca-Cola publications, 1973-1994; 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
  - Columbia Journalism Review 25th Anniversary Issue, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Comics, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Delaney Report, 2004 December (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Flake: 25 Best Cereal Boxes of All Time, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Forgotten Laughter: The Fred Allen Story (Neil Grauer), 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Fortune cover with Joan Collins, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Fox Candy Store/Fastlane, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - FTC Staff Report: Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Gannett/USA Today Directory, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Global Gay Media Proposal for Tribe Magazine, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Gotham Inside Out, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Greatest Moments in TV History, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Hearst: 30 Days of Fashion--Choices: The Art of Getting Ready curated by John A. Bennette, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hearst: A Century in Journalism (James O'Donnell), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Hidden History of Product Placement (Newell, Salmon Chang), 2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - History Factory, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Hotwired deck, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - House Garden--Eclectic Style: The Elements of U, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - How a Publicity Blitz Created the Myth of Subliminal Advertising (Stuart Rogers), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Hunter College, Roosevelt House, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - I'd Like to Force the World to Sing: The Making of a Yes Generation (Joshua Glenn), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - In the Forties (Atlantic Magazine), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Independents (Absolut Vodka), 1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - John Held holiday design, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Kraft 75th Anniversary Anecdote and Trivia Quiz, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Learn to Draw with Jon Gnacy, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Levi's postcards, booklet, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - LGBT miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Los Angeles Advocate, 1967 September (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Luring Green Consumers (Michael Freitag), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mad Magazine 50th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Maidenform: A Company Built by a Brand, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Map: Pearl Harbor attack, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Maps, 1940-1996 and undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mascots Amok (Stinson Carter), undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Masters of the Name Game (naming cars; Bill Kalb), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - MetLife--Out Aging: The MetLife Study of Lesbian and Gay Baby Boomers, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous articles on press and print media, 1975-1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mew York American Marketing Association: Building Brands during Uncertain Times, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - New York Blade News--Times Reaches Out to Gay Readers (Tom McGeveran), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - New York Mets calendar, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - New York New York calendar, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - New York Observer--Fame and Obscurity at the New York Times (Doree Shafrir), undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New York Post--Scooby-Doo special collector's edition, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - New York Times--40th anniversary of moon landing, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New York Times--Advertising's Youth Brigade Flouts Tradition (Randall Rothenberg), 1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - New York Times--Ahead of the Times, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - New York Times--Buick Turns 100, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - New York Times Building flipbook, circa 2007 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - New York Times--Hercule Poirot obituary, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - New York Times notepad with Elliott biography, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - New York Times--The Day the Boy Fell from the Sky (Barbara Lewnes/Stephen Baltz), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - New York Times--Times Fax Monday Media Edition, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - New Yorker--Advertising statistics, circa 1975 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - New Yorker--Every Four Years, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Newsweek--60 Years of Editorial Innovation, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Not a Cough in a Carload (Exhibition of old tobacco ads), 2008 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Out Professionals directory, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - People Weekly Extra: 100 Years of Hollywood, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers Financial Performance Report for Food, Beverage and Consumer Products Industry, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Press Lord (Rupert Murdoch) Captures Gotham (David Gelman), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for Psychological Research Study on the Sale and Consumption of Liquor (Ernest Dichter), 1952 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Radar--Premier issue and promotional materials, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reclaiming the High Line, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Rituals slide show, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Robert Thrumbull reports on salvage operations at Pearl Harbor, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Rolling Stone: The Complete Covers 1967-1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sledge Hammer (Marvel) issue 1, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Sports Illustrated 1954-1994: How We Got Here (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sports Illustrated Olympics issue, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Ten Best American Dailies, 1974-1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The Man Who Discovered Quality [W. Edwards Deming] (Andrea Gabor) excerpt, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Man Who Undressed Men (profile of Bruce Weber, by Peter Davis), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Mood Factory (Adam Hanft), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Story of Chewing Gum--Warner-Lambert, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Word on HIV (Reyataz), 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Time 100: 100 Great Things, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - TV Digest, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Vanity Fair: The Early Years 1914-1936, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Wall Street Journal: Year 1000 special edition, 1999 January 11 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who in Advertising, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Wired: Sample the Future, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - You Are Not Alone (Gay Men's Health Crisis/GMHC, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Subject Files, 1875-2014 and undated; 5
  - 7-Up, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Arnell Group, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Bullett, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Advertising--Agencies--DDB Needham, 1969-2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Della Femina, 1969-1996 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Deutsch, 1988-1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Advertising--Agencies--DMB, 1985-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Doner, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Euro-RSCG (BETC), 2010 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Fallon McElligott, 1988-1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Goodby, Silverstein, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Hayseed House, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Interpublic Group, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Advertising--Agencies--J. Walter Thompson/JWT, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Advertising--Agencies--JWT/Charlotte Beers, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Advertising--Agencies--Leo Burnett, 1936-1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)